var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "لِإِيلَافِ",
        "answer": "For (the) familiarity",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "liīlāfi",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "106",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِيلَافِهِمْ",
        "answer": "Their familiarity",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "īlāfihim",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "106",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "The One Who",
        "pcklId": "1436",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "106",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآمَنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "and gives them security",
        "pcklId": "556",
        "tlit": "waāmanahum",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "106",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَيْتِ",
        "answer": "House",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "l-bayti",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "106",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُوعٍ",
        "answer": "(against) hunger",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "jūʿin",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "106",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَوْفٍ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "khawfin",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "106",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّ",
        "answer": "(the) Lord",
        "pcklId": "970",
        "tlit": "rabba",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "106",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِحْلَةَ",
        "answer": "(with the) journey",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "riḥ'lata",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "106",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشِّتَاءِ",
        "answer": "(of) winter",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-shitāi",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "106",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالصَّيْفِ",
        "answer": "and summer",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wal-ṣayfi",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "106",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَطْعَمَهُمْ",
        "answer": "feeds them",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "aṭʿamahum",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "106",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلْيَعْبُدُوا",
        "answer": "So let them worship",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "falyaʿbudū",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "106",
        "ayah": "3"
    }
]; 
export default words;